Software Engineer

JAMIE LEVINER

 \searrow

levinerjamie@gmail.com

U (843) 229-

1193

iamieleviner.com

jamieleviner

EXPERIENCE

ACS Technologies

Software Engineer | July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

ACS Technologies

Software Engineer-Associate | July 2016 - July 2017

Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

ACS Technologies

Software Development Apprentice | August 2015 - July 2016

Making coffee and baking cookies.

ACS Technologies

Intern | May 2015 - August 2016

EDUCATION

Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics | January

2011 - December 2014

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- jQuery
- VueJS

- CSS/LESS/SASS
- C#/ASP.NET MVC
- Go

- Intercom
- PostgreSQL

About me

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.